Once you have a custom plugin written and the correct CSS
カスタムプラグインを記述し、 CSSとJavaScriptファイルを
and JavaScript files created, it's time to use it.
作成したら、それらを 実装していきます。
You have two choices--
Studioでプラグイン を実装するか、
implementing the plugin in Studio or via code.
コードで実装するか、 2つの選択肢があります。
The nice thing about using Studio
Studioを使用する 利点は、プレーヤーを
is that you need no other code on the page
使用するページに 他のコードが
on which the player is used.
必要ない事です。
What you sacrifice is easier modification.
一方、修正がしにくい という点があります。
When you implement a custom plugin in code,
カスタムプラグインを コードで実装する場合、
it's easier to pass data to the plugin
プラグインがオプションを 受け付けるように
than if you implement it in Studio--
記述されている場合よりも、 プラグインに
that is, if the plugin is written to accept options.
データを渡すのが 容易になります。
Let's implement a custom plugin in Studio.
それでは、Studioにカスタムプラグイン を実装してみましょう。
I will go to Studio's Players module
Studioの Playerモジュールで
and either create a new player or choose
新規プレーヤーを 作成するか、
an existing player in which to implement the plugin.
プラグインを実装する既存の プレーヤーを選択します。
Once in the Players properties, click on the Plugin section.
プレーヤーのプロパティに移動したら 「プロパティ」の項目をクリックします。
In the UI for plugins, we will add a custom plugin.
プラグインのUIで カスタムプラグインを追加します。
For our plugin, we'll provide a name, JavaScript URL,
プラグインには、名前、 JavaScriptのURL,
and the CSS URL.
CSSのURLを指定します。
This particular custom plugin uses no options.
このカスタムプラグインでは、 オプションは使用しません。
Now click Save, publish the player,
次に、「保存」を クリックして
and the enhanced player is ready to go.
プレーヤーを公開すると、拡張された プレーヤーが使用できるようになります。
Now remember, any time this player is used,
このプレーヤーを使用する 時は、常にカスタムプラグイン
it will now contain the custom plugin's functionality.
の機能が含まれている事 に注意してください。